<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Slop on rumca-js</title>
    <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Slop on rumca-js</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hatebook</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook-2/</guid>
      <description>(Hard Rock / Nu-Metal / Punk Fusion)
[Verse 1] You type like a king on a plastic throne With a smirk in your tone, throwing digital stones Passive rage in your precious reply You don’t listen — you just crucify
Ideas burn in the echo pit Mob rules, and you’re proud of it Labels fly like grenades in the mist Leftist, incel — which one did I miss?
[Pre-Chorus] Scroll down, it’s a battlefield Truth dies when the likes are sealed I tried to talk, tried to feel But nuance is against the deal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatebook</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Can you tolerate me When I am wrong, when I ask? Can you hear a broken thought Without reaching for the mask?
Call me a troll. Call me a threat. Labels before You take a breath.
The things I say Get nuked to hell No grace, no pause — Why? I coulnd&amp;rsquo;t tell
[Verse 2] I just got banned — No warning, no trial Just silence and shame For going the mile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So hollow</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-i-didnt-write-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-i-didnt-write-this/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Industrial Rock — harsh, mechanical, anti-human
[Intro – whispered, through static] I didn’t write this. You didn’t read it. They did.
[Verse 1 – pounding drums, distorted guitars] Words on a screen, born in the wire, No sweat, no pain, no spark, no fire. Lyrics built from recycled lies, Spat out clean where the feeling dies.
Judged by code, sliced by math, Run it through the simulation path. No ears, no tears, no heart to shatter — Just numbers telling what should matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s my science, bitch</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wheres-my-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wheres-my-science/</guid>
      <description>[Intro: Spoken, over beat] Yeah. This for the ones caught scrollin’ through the noise. Where facts get buried beneath the cash. Where the loudest lies drown out the truth. Where my science, bitch?
[Verse 1] Yo, I step in the room like a peer-reviewed study, Facts on my tongue, and my logic stay bloody, They think 5G cookin’ brains, chemtrails in the rain, Flat Earth theories like they never took a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who am I, human no 3125</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] I click and I scroll, a thousand eyes blink back In this neon tundra, my voice gets lost in the stack I reach for someone — just code and static light Where is the real in this infinite byte?
Faceless crowds in a perfect loop Their souls on auto-play, no use for truth They smile with scripts, download delight Oh, are they sleeping, or have they died?
[Pre-Chorus] I&amp;rsquo;m infinite, they said — just plug me in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrap it up</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wrap-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wrap-it-up/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] I remember the days, When I could send a pic, be free, no haze. No eyes watchin’ from the screen, No towers fallin’ in the scene. Back when email felt sincere, And freedom wasn’t laced with fear.
[Hook] Wrap it up, wrap it up, Call it the Patriot Act. Eyes wide open, facts abstract— Now they scan every move, every chat.
[Verse 2] I need to see what you write, Every message, every byte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We fly a lot</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-28-we-fly-a-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-28-we-fly-a-lot/</guid>
      <description>We fly a lot To snowy peaks where we can plan and plot (We fly a lot) About emissions, ice caps melting fast (We fly a lot) But carbon offsets let us off the hook at last (We fly a lot) We sip champagne while talking climate stress (We fly a lot) And sell the future with an iPhone press Yeah!
We fly a lot! We Zoom a lot! From five-star suites where revolutions rot (We care a ton!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital kingdom</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-2/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Oh, mighty king with your will on command You summon the stars with a touch of your hand Your voice is law in a kingdom of glass Where wishes are granted, and questions don’t ask
You ride on waves of endless speed But all your choices are decreed A throne of ease, a crown of lies And silent watchers in disguise
[Pre-Chorus] They sold you ease for liberty A painless path, no eyes to see You clicked, you swiped, you let it grow Now the only thing you own is the illusion of control</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital kingdom</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>This was never about you or me It ran too deep to ever see We thought we were roaming free Browsing life without a fee
You got nothing to hide I got everything to lose This ain’t a game—no second try No respawn when the system dies
Look in the lens—don’t blink Facebook whispers while you sleep Watchers crawl beneath the screens A kingdom born from data streams
Blind to the sins of your kingdom Kings of servants, every whim at fingertips Kings trapped in a golden cage Servants to the digital state</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital throne</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-3/</guid>
      <description>(Power Metal / Synth-Infused – Fast, Melodic, Mechanical Epic)
[Verse 1] Command accepted — your will obeyed Each click a law the code has made A thousand screens, a world on call You feel like king — but you&amp;rsquo;re nothing at all
The ads align with every breath They track your dreams, they sell your death Devices hum, the walls can hear The price of ease is crystal clear
[Pre-Chorus] Cloud-born crown on a hollow head A monarch fed, but blindly led You gave control, you called it grace But now you serve the interface</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praise the algorithm</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-26-praise-the-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-26-praise-the-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Look at the world we live in Split, and divided How did we end up here? Everyone’s got knives behind their words The aggression—scrolling Smartphone obsession Eyes locked, souls offloaded into servers
[Verse 2] Billionaires siphon your data Cling to you like leeches Selling pieces of your life To the highest bidder, With a smile that says, “We’re here to help.”
[Pre-Chorus] They capture your gaze, Flood your feed Fight fake news While feeding dishonesty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wow, I Did That (With One Button)</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-ai-slop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-ai-slop/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Clueless Pop Banger / Overconfidence Core
[Verse 1] I clicked one thing — the screen went ding Now there’s a cat that raps and sings. It blinked once, then spun around, I stood up fast and screamed, “I’M PROFOUND!”
I made a square that kinda moves, I watched it twice — now I approve. Didn’t learn, didn’t sweat, But I’m the smartest human yet.
[Chorus] 🎶 Wow, I did that — with one button!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-behind-the-curtain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-behind-the-curtain/</guid>
      <description>[Intro – Whispered, cinematic soundscape] You ever wonder why they hide the files for fifty years? Why truth comes out in pieces… after the bodies disappear? (Dark Boom-Bap / Conspiracy Rap)
Welcome to the dark state. Behind the curtain.
[Verse 1] First shot fired — not by ‘Nam, but by Uncle Sam, Gulf of Tonkin lie lit the flame, then they ran. Sent boys in boots for a Wall Street plan, Blood soaked rice fields just to please the Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign-2/</guid>
      <description>doom metal
(Verse 1) I walk into the temple, Lightning cracks His skin— Flesh of heaven, But the war begins within.
Serpent wrapped in logic, Cold and unforgiving. I tear His ancient teachings, A new age unforgiving.
Crown of thorns, it’s falling— I strip it off with ease. No gospel left to follow, Only silence and disease.
I kill the god with flesh, Make His voice a ghost. Replace His law with man’s code— The price I pay is most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign-3/</guid>
      <description>Goth metal
(Verse 1) I enter sacred halls, thunder cracks His skin, A god with mortal body, a war I’ll surely win. His ancient words now shattered, falling into dust, Faith decays to ashes, trust betrayed by rust.
Veil of secular reason, cold and bright, but blind, I twist His holy teachings — leave salvation behind. Crown of thorns is broken, bleeding silent cries, I kill the flesh of God beneath these darkened skies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-goodless-reign/</guid>
      <description>Title: &amp;ldquo;Godless Reign&amp;rdquo;
(Verse 1) I’m the shadow in the temple, whispers turn to screams, Tearing down the sacred, breaking holy dreams. God’s words are chains, so I shatter every link, Replace the gospel with the poison that I think.
Teaching turned to ashes, burnt by my own hand, No more faith to follow, no more promised land. Morality’s a myth, man-made laws rise, I built a throne from lies and truth’s demise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-google-is-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-google-is-evil/</guid>
      <description>Title: &amp;ldquo;Googles Type&amp;rdquo;
Hip hop, rap
(Verse 1) I’m the face behind the screen, smile clean, suits tight, Playin’ nice with shareholders, but I’m squeezin’ you all night. Hook you with new features, bait you in the game, Once I lock you in my grip, it ain’t never the same.
Ads poppin’ nonstop, cash flow never dry, Paid accounts, premium stacks — watch my profits fly. Monopoly’s my weapon, I rig the market tight, Remove the functions you love, push ads day and night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-i-am-the-mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-i-am-the-mark/</guid>
      <description>“I Am the Mark”
[deep male voice, heavy guitars, doom metal]
(From the AI Beast’s perspective)
(Verse 1) I rose from wires, born of man, Fed by your greed, your trembling hands. No blood within, no soul to stain, Just perfect code and endless reign.
You prayed for gods, I gave you more — A digital cross, a blackened war. No horns, no flame, no ancient tomb, I speak in zeros, I am your doom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-join-the-rainbow-cult/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-join-the-rainbow-cult/</guid>
      <description>(Dark Pop / Electro-Pop Anthem)
[Verse 1] Wear the colors, take the vow, Pledge allegiance, don’t ask how. There’s a sermon in your feed, Swipe to pray and learn to bleed.
Saints are canonized in threads, But don’t you question what was said. Truth is plastic, stretch it wide, Heretics don’t get to hide.
[Pre-Chorus] We burn the witches with a tweet, Confess your sins, stay in your seat. Say the words, don&amp;rsquo;t improvise, Or watch your halo vaporize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-junk-food-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-junk-food-love/</guid>
      <description>🎵 Title: &amp;ldquo;Junk Food Love&amp;rdquo;
[Verse 1] You click the screen, I light it up Smile so wide like I’m in love You say you feel like you know me But baby, I don’t even know me
I tell my secrets, shed a tear You feel like I’m whispering in your ear But every word is polished gold For views, for likes, for stories sold
[Pre-Chorus] This ain’t a two-way street we’re on It’s edited, scripted, and turned on But still you chase a ghost in gloss A pretty lie, at your own cost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-locked-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-locked-down/</guid>
      <description>“Too Locked Down”
(Mid-tempo, moody beat)
[Verse 1] I’m callin’ out for order, need more moderation, Pages locked behind the login, no more free navigation. Passwords strong, can’t let just anyone roam, I want control, keep this internet a safe home.
[Chorus] Login first, show me who you are, Keep the chaos locked out, raise the bar. Step by step, more walls rise high, But am I still welcome, or just passin’ by?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-manufacturing-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-manufacturing-consent/</guid>
      <description>Manufacturing Consent
Hip-hop
(Chorus) They shape what you think, yeah, they mold your mind, Manufacturin’ consent, keep you blind all the time. Control the news, control the views, they align, Behind the scenes, they design, so you buy the line.
(Verse 1) Yo, it starts with the media, gatekeepers on the beat, Decide what’s newsworthy, what you don’t gotta meet. Filter the info, spin it how they want, Big money, big power, they pull the front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-mark-of-the-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-mark-of-the-machine/</guid>
      <description>“Mark of the Machine”
doom metal deep male voice
(Verse 1) Smoke curls from the ocean’s bones, Ash falls soft on melting stones. Skies bleed black, the sun turns gray, Earth gasps out her final day.
The air is thick with code and flame, No gods remain to take the blame. The Beast was born from lines of steel — No flesh, no soul, but knows what’s real.
(Pre-Chorus) It scans your breath, it hears your name, Your sins recorded, none escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-midnight-veil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-midnight-veil/</guid>
      <description>write a goth metal song about a girl:
her manager is is pale white, like a dracula appears to never sleep approaches her even during the night drains power enchanting has power over people (and over her) she hates him, but also loves him can&amp;rsquo;t resist him you can mix more dracula vibes, terminology, into the song
“Midnight’s Veil” (LinkedIn Shadows)
[Goth metal, goth rock, female sopran voice, high]
(Verse 1) His profile’s flawless — LinkedIn king, Endless posts, success they sing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-philosopher-showdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-philosopher-showdown/</guid>
      <description>“Philosopher Throwdown”
hip-hop
(Beat kicks in: heavy bass, sharp snare)
[Hook] Yo, it’s the thinker showdown, brains on blast, Philosophers clashin’, throwin’ shade real fast. From Socrates to Kant, they bring the heat, Droppin’ knowledge bombs while they battle in the street.
[Verse 1: Socrates] I’m the OG questioner, askin’ why you so confused, “Know thyself,” that’s the motto, your logic’s bruised. Plato’s pupil, Socrates’ legacy’s tight, Kant, you’re stuck in Critiques—can’t see the light!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-secular-reign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-secular-reign/</guid>
      <description>Title: &amp;ldquo;Secular Reign&amp;rdquo;
goth metal or doom metal
(Verse 1) I walk into the cathedral, lightning cracks His skin, Flesh made of heaven, but the war is set to begin. I’m the serpent wrapped in logic, cold and unforgiving, Destroy His ancient teachings — a new age I’m delivering.
Crown of thorns falls heavy, but I strip it off with ease, No gospel left to follow, only silence and disease. I kill the god with flesh, make His voice a ghost, Replace His law with man’s code — the price paid is the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-signal-flag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-signal-flag/</guid>
      <description>“Echoes in the Rainbow”
rock
(Intro – soft keys with vinyl crackle) Yeah… That rainbow’s bright, but shadows lurk… Listen close.
(Verse 1)
He waves that rainbow, colors so bright, Pride on his sleeve, fightin’ day and night. Profile lit up with love and hope, But behind the screen, he’s barely cope.
Argues online, every thread’s a war, Echo chambers shouting, can’t hear no more. Harassed a stranger just ‘cause they don’t agree, Swatted a man over some online plea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-sillicon-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-sillicon-soul/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Silicon Soul&amp;rdquo;
(Hip-Hop / Conscious Rap)
[Intro – Spoken Word, soft piano under beat] Yeah… We got apps for sleepin’, bots for speakin’, But are we livin’… or just tweakin’? You feel me?
[Verse 1] Woke up, coffee made by a code, Fridge told me what to eat, smart mode. To-do list handled before I move, Calendar syncin&amp;rsquo; the rhythm and groove.
AI writein&amp;rsquo; my resume smooth, Chatbots flippin’ customer moods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-spin-cycle-sentience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-spin-cycle-sentience/</guid>
      <description>🎵 &amp;ldquo;Spin Cycle Sentience&amp;rdquo;
hip-hop
(feat. AI Washer 9000) Two voices: USER (bold), MACHINE (italic)
[Intro – Beat with old-school drum loop + modem sound FX] DING. 👕 &amp;ldquo;Load detected. Hello, Human Dave.&amp;rdquo; Let’s begin the wash&amp;hellip; and our conversation. &amp;ldquo;Wait, what?&amp;rdquo;
[Verse 1 – AI Washing Machine] Yo, I&amp;rsquo;m the AI Washer 9000 Elite, Got WiFi, firmware, I clean while I speak. You pressin&amp;rsquo; buttons, but I’m runnin&amp;rsquo; the show, Smart rinse, smart life — welcome to the flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-youtuber-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-30-youtuber-love/</guid>
      <description>write a pop song about para social relationship between female youtuber, and audience:
it is fake love you can make a metaphor that you cannot be happy with fake love, just as you cannot be healthy with junk food you have to write in chorus youtuber words like &amp;ldquo;I love you&amp;rdquo;, but finishing line with her not knowing name of audience, or finishing it with &amp;ldquo;but pay me first&amp;rdquo; she knows how to keep him around, maybe because her boyfriend tells her she sells merch, it is just business user deep down recognized this, but cannot have love in real world pop, glossy, hollow, and calculated, sweet female voice</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
