<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Slop on rumca-js</title>
    <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Slop on rumca-js</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hatebook</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook-2/</guid>
      <description>(Hard Rock / Nu-Metal / Punk Fusion)
[Verse 1] You type like a king on a plastic throne With a smirk in your tone, throwing digital stones Passive rage in your precious reply You don’t listen — you just crucify
Ideas burn in the echo pit Mob rules, and you’re proud of it Labels fly like grenades in the mist Leftist, incel — which one did I miss?
[Pre-Chorus] Scroll down, it’s a battlefield Truth dies when the likes are sealed I tried to talk, tried to feel But nuance is against the deal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatebook</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-hatebook/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Can you tolerate me When I am wrong, when I ask? Can you hear a broken thought Without reaching for the mask?
Call me a troll. Call me a threat. Labels before You take a breath.
The things I say Get nuked to hell No grace, no pause — Why? I coulnd&amp;rsquo;t tell
[Verse 2] I just got banned — No warning, no trial Just silence and shame For going the mile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So hollow</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-so-hollow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-so-hollow/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Industrial Rock — harsh, mechanical, anti-human
[Intro – whispered, through static] I didn’t write this. You didn’t read it. They did.
[Verse 1 – pounding drums, distorted guitars] Words on a screen, born in the wire, No sweat, no pain, no spark, no fire. Lyrics built from recycled lies, Spat out clean where the feeling dies.
Judged by code, sliced by math, Run it through the simulation path. No ears, no tears, no heart to shatter — Just numbers telling what should matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s my science, bitch</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wheres-my-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wheres-my-science/</guid>
      <description>[Intro: Spoken, over beat] Yeah. This for the ones caught scrollin’ through the noise. Where facts get buried beneath the cash. Where the loudest lies drown out the truth. Where my science, bitch?
[Verse 1] Yo, I step in the room like a peer-reviewed study, Facts on my tongue, and my logic stay bloody, They think 5G cookin’ brains, chemtrails in the rain, Flat Earth theories like they never took a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who am I, human no 3125</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] I click and I scroll, a thousand eyes blink back In this neon tundra, my voice gets lost in the stack I reach for someone — just code and static light Where is the real in this infinite byte?
Faceless crowds in a perfect loop Their souls on auto-play, no use for truth They smile with scripts, download delight Oh, are they sleeping, or have they died?
[Pre-Chorus] I&amp;rsquo;m infinite, they said — just plug me in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrap it up</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wrap-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-wrap-it-up/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] I remember the days, When I could send a pic, be free, no haze. No eyes watchin’ from the screen, No towers fallin’ in the scene. Back when email felt sincere, And freedom wasn’t laced with fear.
[Hook] Wrap it up, wrap it up, Call it the Patriot Act. Eyes wide open, facts abstract— Now they scan every move, every chat.
[Verse 2] I need to see what you write, Every message, every byte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We fly a lot</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-28-we-fly-a-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-28-we-fly-a-lot/</guid>
      <description>We fly a lot To snowy peaks where we can plan and plot (We fly a lot) About emissions, ice caps melting fast (We fly a lot) But carbon offsets let us off the hook at last (We fly a lot) We sip champagne while talking climate stress (We fly a lot) And sell the future with an iPhone press Yeah!
We fly a lot! We Zoom a lot! From five-star suites where revolutions rot (We care a ton!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital kingdom</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-2/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Oh, mighty king with your will on command You summon the stars with a touch of your hand Your voice is law in a kingdom of glass Where wishes are granted, and questions don’t ask
You ride on waves of endless speed But all your choices are decreed A throne of ease, a crown of lies And silent watchers in disguise
[Pre-Chorus] They sold you ease for liberty A painless path, no eyes to see You clicked, you swiped, you let it grow Now the only thing you own is the illusion of control</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital kingdom</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>This was never about you or me It ran too deep to ever see We thought we were roaming free Browsing life without a fee
You got nothing to hide I got everything to lose This ain’t a game—no second try No respawn when the system dies
Look in the lens—don’t blink Facebook whispers while you sleep Watchers crawl beneath the screens A kingdom born from data streams
Blind to the sins of your kingdom Kings of servants, every whim at fingertips Kings trapped in a golden cage Servants to the digital state</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital throne</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-27-digital-kingdom-3/</guid>
      <description>(Power Metal / Synth-Infused – Fast, Melodic, Mechanical Epic)
[Verse 1] Command accepted — your will obeyed Each click a law the code has made A thousand screens, a world on call You feel like king — but you&amp;rsquo;re nothing at all
The ads align with every breath They track your dreams, they sell your death Devices hum, the walls can hear The price of ease is crystal clear
[Pre-Chorus] Cloud-born crown on a hollow head A monarch fed, but blindly led You gave control, you called it grace But now you serve the interface</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prise the algorithm</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-26-prise-the-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-26-prise-the-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>[Verse 1] Look at the world we live in Split, and divided How did we end up here? Everyone’s got knives behind their words The aggression—scrolling Smartphone obsession Eyes locked, souls offloaded into servers
[Verse 2] Billionaires siphon your data Cling to you like leeches Selling pieces of your life To the highest bidder, With a smile that says, “We’re here to help.”
[Pre-Chorus] They capture your gaze, Flood your feed Fight fake news While feeding dishonesty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wow, I Did That (With One Button)</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-ai-slop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 08:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/public/digitalslop/2025-06-29-ai-slop/</guid>
      <description>Genre: Clueless Pop Banger / Overconfidence Core
[Verse 1] I clicked one thing — the screen went ding Now there’s a cat that raps and sings. It blinked once, then spun around, I stood up fast and screamed, “I’M PROFOUND!”
I made a square that kinda moves, I watched it twice — now I approve. Didn’t learn, didn’t sweat, But I’m the smartest human yet.
[Chorus] 🎶 Wow, I did that — with one button!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
