<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My name is rumca-js</title>
    <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My name is rumca-js</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Awesome lists</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-21-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-21-awesome/</guid>
      <description>For some time now, I’ve been exploring awesome lists.
If you’re not familiar with them, awesome lists are curated collections of resources, tools, libraries, tutorials, and other valuable content, typically centered around a specific topic or theme. They are usually created by developers or enthusiasts and hosted on GitHub, making them easily accessible and open for contributions.
Examples:
https://github.com/sindresorhus/awesome https://github.com/awesome-selfhosted/awesome-selfhosted What fascinates me is why such lists exist in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bug problem</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-13-table-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-13-table-problem/</guid>
      <description>Another amusing yet frustrating incident occurred recently.
I discovered a particularly nasty bug in my code - it froze the entire app after exactly 10 page refreshes. I was initially baffled and unsure where to start debugging.
I’m no Python expert, and my main safety net is a solid suite of unit tests. These help a lot, but they don’t catch issues like memory leaks or recursion problems. Clearly, I still have a lot to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table problem</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-14-bug-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-14-bug-problem/</guid>
      <description>here was this one time I got up and checked my webpage. It&amp;rsquo;s a habit of mine—checking, making sure everything is up and running. I&amp;rsquo;m not doing it for anyone else. Nobody uses my app instances; I’m the sole user. Yet, I&amp;rsquo;m devoted.
That day, I ran into a problem. A table in my database had a data error and became completely unreadable. I tried fixing it—several times. I sifted through pages of documentation and even enlisted ChatGPT for assistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first post</title>
      <link>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-07-my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumca-js.github.io/quickstart/posts/2024-11-07-my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>So it happened. This is my first post.
In this &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; of sorts I will try introducing progress made on my software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
